you get up two and a half million
dollars any in the world knows
dollars any in the world knows what to do you get a house with a
what to do you get a house with a
what to do you get a house with a 25-year roof an indestructible jab
25-year roof an indestructible jab
economy box you put the rest into
economy box you put the rest into the system at three to five percent to
the system at three to five percent to
the system at three to five percent to pay your taxes and that's your base get
pay your taxes and that's your base get
Solitude that puts you for the rest of
your life at a level of you
you boss pisses you off you own
you boss pisses you off you own your house have a couple bucks in the
your house have a couple bucks in the
your house have a couple bucks in the bank don't drink that's all I have to
bank don't drink that's all I have to
bank don't drink that's all I have to say to anybody in any social level does
say to anybody in any social level does
say to anybody in any social level does your grandfather take risks
your grandfather take risks
your grandfather take risks yes I guarantee he did it from a
yes I guarantee he did it from a
position of you
you the United States of America is
based on you you're a king
based on you you're a king you have an army greatest Navy in the
you have an army greatest Navy in the
we'll it up ourselves which we have
done beautiful you possession lost
done beautiful you possession lost forever
forever
because he doesn't know when to say
you I have a car and a house and a
family and it's all paid for you I
family and it's all paid for you I mean even I did that
mean even I did that
mean even I did that wants to stop by Pierre blossom I'll
wants to stop by Pierre blossom I'll
don't put it on me but he did
don't put it on me but he did put it on you miss
put it on you miss
put it on you miss oh
oh
oh you still owe large two places you
you still owe large two places you
you still owe large two places you shouldn't
shouldn't
shouldn't why do you want door number three
why do you want door number three
why do you want door number three how else do I get out Time payments sell
how else do I get out Time payments sell
should I know
should I know I am of the universe and you know what
I am of the universe and you know what
I am of the universe and you know what it's worth it's worth plenty
if I give you this money
if I give you this money and you don't pay me back there are no
and you don't pay me back there are no
and you don't pay me back there are no rules
rules
you never get to say you to anybody
you never get to say you to anybody ever
it would get me not just what you owe me
it would get me not just what you owe me from your family he will give me their
from your family he will give me their
from your family he will give me their accounts so I can have them vacuum from
accounts so I can have them vacuum from
accounts so I can have them vacuum from Russia you jump off a bridge you can do
Russia you jump off a bridge you can do
Russia you jump off a bridge you can do it knowing I will kill your entire
it knowing I will kill your entire
it knowing I will kill your entire bloodline
bloodline
bloodline you understand the gravity of your
you understand the gravity of your
you understand the gravity of your situation
260 is requested
260 is requested what's this
what's this
what's this much money what's a car
[Music]
[Music] foreign
foreign
foreign [Music]