You get up two and a half million dollars.
Any asshole in the world knows what to do.
You get a house for the 25-year roof,
an indestructible, jab-economy, ship box.
You put the rest into the system of three to five percent
to pay your taxes and that's your base.
Get me?
That's your fortress of fucking solitude.
That puts you for the rest of your life at a level of fuck you.
Somebody wants you to do something, fuck you.
Boss Pissas, you are fuck you on your house.
Have a couple bucks in the bank.
Don't drink.
That's all I have to say to anybody in any social level.
Is your grandfather take risks?
Yes.
I guarantee you he did it from a position of fuck you.
A wise man's life is based around fuck you.
The United States of America is based on fuck you.
You're a king.
You have an army, greatest navy in the history of the world.
Fuck you, Blooming.
Fuck it up ourselves.
Which we have done beautiful fuck you position
lost forever.
Hey, George, the third looks like a fucking birthday present.
This is the grandson of the 17th richest man in California.
Does he drink?
What he wants is money because he doesn't know
when to say that's it.
I'm two million ahead, fuck it, fuck you.
I have a car in a house and a family
and it's all paid for fuck you.
I mean, even I did that.
What's your stop by, pay a blossom?
I have a beer just thinking anybody else, thank you.
What kind?
Any kind.
You got 37 beers.
Don't fucking put it on me.
But he did put it on you, Miss.
You still owe large two places you shouldn't.
Why do you want door number three?
How else do I get out?
I ain't payment.
Sell your sperm.
Sell your ass.
How the fuck should I know?
I am of the universe and you know what it's worth.
Worth plenty.
If I give you this money and you don't pay me back,
there are no rules.
You never get to say fuck you to anybody ever.
You will get me not just what you owe me from your family.
You will get me their accounts so I can have them vacuum
from Russia.
You jump off a bridge.
You can do it knowing I will kill your entire blood
and your whole life.
Do you understand the gravity of your situation?
I understand.
You get up, you get out.
260 is requested.
What's this?
This much money, what's a car?
What do you want to be able to say to me?
Fuck you.