You get up to an hour and a half million dollars.
Any asshole in the world knows what to do.
You get a house with a 25-year group
and then distractable, jab economy, shitbox.
You put the rest into the system.
A 3-5% to pay your taxes and that's your base.
Get me at your fortress of fucking solitude.
That puts you for the rest of your life at a level of fuck you.
Somebody wants you to do something. Fuck you.
Boss paces you off. Fuck you.
Own your house.
Have a couple bucks in a bank.
Don't drink.
That's all I have to say to anybody in any social level.
Would you grant father take risks?
Yes.
I guarantee you did it from a position of fuck you.
The wise man's life is based around fuck you.
The United States of America is based on fuck you.
You're a king.
You have an army?
Greatest navy in the history of the world?
Fuck you.
Blowing, fuck it up ourselves.
Which we have done.
Beautiful, fuck you position, lost forever.
King George III looks like a fucking birthday present.
This is the grandson of the 17th richest man in California.
Does he drink?
What do you want?
His money.
Because he doesn't know when to say that's it.
I'm 2 million I had.
Fuck it.
Fuck you.
I have a car and a house and a family.
And it's all paid for.
Fuck you.
I mean, even I did that.
What's your job by pay a blossom?
I have a beard just thinking anybody else.
Thank you.
What kind?
Any kind.
About 37 beers.
Don't fucking put it on me.
What he did put it on you mess?
You still owe a large two places you shouldn't.
Why do you want to owe number three?
I lost them.
I get out.
I ain't payment.
So you're sperm.
So you're as high the fuck should I know.
I am of the universe and you know what it's worth.
It's worth plenty.
If I give you this money and you don't pay me back.
There are no rules.
You never get to say fuck you to anybody ever.
You will get me not just what you owe me from your family.
You will get me their accounts so I can have them vacuum from Russia.
You jump off a bridge.
You can do it knowing I will kill your entire bloodline.
You understand the gravity of your situation.
I understand.
You get up, you get out.
Two sixties requested.
What's that?
This much money once a car.
What do you want to be able to say to me?
Fuck you.