You get up to an hour and a half million dollars.
You get a house with a 25-year group
You put the rest into the system.
A 3-5% to pay your taxes and that's your base.
Own your house.
Have a couple bucks in a bank.
Don't drink.
That's all I have to say to anybody in any social level.
Would you grant father take risks?
Yes.
You're a king.
You have an army?
Greatest navy in the history of the world?
Which we have done.
This is the grandson of the 17th richest man in California.
Does he drink?
What do you want?
His money.
Because he doesn't know when to say that's it.
I'm 2 million I had.
I have a car and a house and a family.
And it's all paid for.
I mean, even I did that.
What's your job by pay a blossom?
I have a beard just thinking anybody else.
Thank you.
What kind?
Any kind.
About 37 beers.
What he did put it on you mess?
You still owe a large two places you shouldn't.
Why do you want to owe number three?
I lost them.
I get out.
I ain't payment.
I am of the universe and you know what it's worth.
It's worth plenty.
If I give you this money and you don't pay me back.
There are no rules.
You will get me not just what you owe me from your family.
You will get me their accounts so I can have them vacuum from Russia.
You jump off a bridge.
You can do it knowing I will kill your entire bloodline.
You understand the gravity of your situation.
I understand.
You get up, you get out.
Two sixties requested.
What's that?
This much money once a car.
What do you want to be able to say to me?